<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VPaksh</title>
    <description>Say No! To Fake News!</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 20:42:39 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 20:42:39 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harish Meena’s joining Congress is an unfair step, says BJP
East Coast Daily</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;BJP national spokesperson Sudhanshu Trivedi said that BJP Harish Chandra Meena MP joining Congress is an unfair step. The party had given him a lot, but he chose to quit it in “an unfair step”, he said. His decision to leave the party, however, will make no difference to it, he added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harish Meena, BJP’s Dausa MP, joined the Congress in Delhi in the presence of former Rajasthan chief minister Ashok Gehlot, Rajasthan Congress chief Sachin Pilot and AICC’s state in-charge Avinash Pande on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harish Meena, a former IPS officer and Rajasthan DGP, had joined the BJP ahead of the 2014 Lok Sabha polls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congress leader and Sapotara MLA Ramesh Meena said though his party had given a lot to the family of Namonain Meena, his brother Harish Meena joined the BJP in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harish Meena has returned home, said the deputy leader of opposition in the state assembly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harish Meena was DGP during Gehlot’s tenure as chief minister and was pitted by the BJP against his brother Namonarain in the 2014 Lok Sabha elections from the Dausa constituency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had won the seat by defeating his nearest rival Kirori Lal Meena, who was then a candidate of the National People’s Party, by a margin of 45,404 votes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His brother Namonarai Meena, then a Union minister, had stood third in the result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talking about the “tussle” within the Congress over ticket distribution, Trivedi said its state leaders have already announced their candidature for assembly polls even before the party declaring its candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said while Congress general secretary Ashok Gehlot and party’s state chief Sachin Pilot have announced to contest, another leader Harish Chaudhary has filed nomination, and it’s all before the declaration of candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congress is taking one step forward and the next step backward. The situation seems awkward. Delay in finalizing the candidates’ list indicates that the ticket distribution is stuck in a tussle over the shares of its top leaders’ candidates in the list, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/12/harish-meenas-joining-congress-is-an-unfair-step-says-bjp-east-coast-daily.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/02/12/harish-meenas-joining-congress-is-an-unfair-step-says-bjp-east-coast-daily.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PM Modi will soon be jailed over Rafale deal</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;PM Modi will soon be jailed over Rafale deal, claims former Karnataka CM Siddaramaiah
VPaksh.in
The Congress has been attacking Modi government for refusing to furnish details of the Rafale deal.
Siddaramaiah was addressing a public rally in Jamakhandi of Bagalkot district in Karnataka on Thursday, November 1 when he made the statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Congress has been attacking Modi government for refusing to furnish details of the Rafale deal. The party accused the government of causing huge loss of taxpayer’s money by signing the deal worth Rs 58,000 crore with French manufacturers Dassault. The party also alleged that the cost of each aircraft is thrice more than the negotiations made by the previous UPA government in 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Siddaramaiah also recalled the time when state BJP president BS Yeddyurappa had gone to jail on alleged corruptions charges and schemes, Deccan Chronicle reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also hit back at the Centre for raising only communal issues mostly based on religious sentiments like Ram temple and Hindutva. He challenged the BJP to seek votes on the basis of the development work carried out by the Modi government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He alleged that the saffron party always believed in communal politics and dividing the nation by raising religiously sensitive issues, the daily reported.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/06/12/pos-1-about-some-random-politics.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/06/12/pos-1-about-some-random-politics.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
